Finding aid to the International Institute for Girls in Spain records CA.MS.00103
Smith College Archives
- Series XV. AFFILIATED AND RELATED ORGANIZATIONS
  - Scrapbooks, 1948-68
    - International Institute League, 1903-23; undated (Box 53, Folder 1051)
    - Residencia de Senoritas, 1929-65 undated (Box 53, Folder 1052)
    - Third Year programs, 1958-78; undated (Box 53, Folder 1053)
- Corresponding secretary's files, 1979-1989 (Box 54)
- Corresponding secretary's files, 1979-1989 (Box 55)
- Records kept by Angela Giral as member of the board, 1987-1993 (Box 56)
- Treasurer's records, A-G, 1974-1983 (Box 57)
- Treasurer's records, H-Z, 1974-1983 (Box 58)